I don't fully understand them
no las entiendo
Johana, do you think we should pray for some of
totalmente Johana te parece que recemos
your moments on Sálvame that
algunos momentos tuyos en sálvame que te
will bring back memories?
van a traer recuerdo
We were talking at the beginning of the
hemos estado hablando al principio del
program about you and your time on Sálvame and you
programa de tu de tu paso por sálvame y
told me that you had beautiful memories.
me has dicho que tenía recuerdos bonitos
No, and I asked my people,
no y le he encargado a mi gente en
especially Tesa. Tesa has helped me. I'm
especial tesa Me ha ayudado tesa Te
sending you a huge hug, she has saved my
mando un abrazo enorme que me ha salvado
life because I have,
y la vida porque tengo
well today I don't even know where I am. Okay, today I
bueno hoy no sé ni dónde estoy vale hoy
don't even know where I am and
no sé ni dónde estoy y
it's more compiled, some moments that will bring back
está más recopilado algunos momentos que
memories. So perfect, let's get
te van a traer recuerdo Así que perfecto
to it,
vamos a ello
very well. Let's see it perfectly.
muy bien Vamos a verlo perfectamente
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Unparalleled and inimitable friend. Don't
inigualable e inimitable amiga No me
compare me with anyone, okay,
compares con nadie vale
the shape that Anabel had. She
la forma que tenía Anabel la forma las
maintains it a little. Today I also
mantiene un poco a día de hoy también te
tell you no. I mean, the shape a little. If they
digo no O sea la forma un poquito Si la
maintain it, Belén, yes, she has calmed down
mantienen Belén sí que se ha calmado lo
a little. You see it a little bit as the years go by, but it's
ves un poco con el paso de los años pero
very funny to me because back
me hace mucha gracia porque en aquel
then, the more she was like that, the more
entonces Cuanto más así era más aplaudía
people applauded, far from reproaching you for anything, they
la gente lejos de reprocharte nada le
applauded the one who had the shape like that.
aplaudía a la que tenía la forma así
The truth is that she had  a lot of support
ella la verdad es que tenía mucho apoyo
look, I once remember that well at
mira yo una vez recuerdo que bueno en
that time people were coming down and asking for
ese momento la gente bajaba y pedían
autographs and such from the collaborators and I
autógrafos y tal a los colaboradores y
remember that a lady said to me I'm a
recuerdo que una señora me dice yo soy
big fan of Belén Esteban and I said Ah
muy fan de Belén Esteban y yo dije Ah
very well that seems perfect to me and she started
muy bien me parece perfecto y se dedicó
walking in front of my table and
a pasearse por delante de mi mesa y una
once she picked up the glass of water and I said I said she's
vez cogió el vaso de agua y yo dije dije
going to smash it on me because I do
me lo va a estampar encima porque otra
n't see anything else and in the end she calmed down and she left
cosa no veo y al final se calmó Y se fue
no at that moment she had support and let's
no en ese momento ella tenía un apoyo y
see there's one thing that I've always
a ver hay una cosa que yo siempre la he
said about Belén and I have never understood
hecho de Belén y yo nunca he entendido
Jesús's position of losing his
la postura de Jesús de perderse a su
eldest daughter I have never understood it
hija mayor nunca la he entendido nunca
because I mean they had an
porque quiero decir Ellos tenían un
agreement he could have gone he could have been
convenio él podía haber ido podía haber
alone with his daughter who is or Belén did
estado solo con su hija que es o Belén
n't oppose and of course who has
tampoco se oponía y claro Quién ha
lost here has been the girl who has not
perdido aquí ha sido la niña que no ha
had a relationship with her father you know I
tenido relación con su padre sabes
even
Incluso
compiled a little because Of course With this
recopilé un poco porque Claro Con esto
documentary by Rocío Carrasco and the
del documental de Rocío Carrasco y las
things that she pointed out about
cosas que ella señalaba de
Antonio Abi it was very comparable to things
Antonio Abi era muy comparables a cosas
that have also been experienced in history
que también se ha vivido en la historia
but on the contrary in three because Belén
pero de contrario en tres porque Belén
Esteban the covers that  has done by
Esteban las portadas que ha hecho
messing with Jesulín and with Campanario
metiéndose con jesulín y con campanario
the programs that he has made as a father
los programas que ha hecho como padre
how has he put it then
como la ha puesto entonces
I would love for you to talk Jesulín
a mí me encantaría que hablaras jesulín
evidently well it was said that he
evidentemente bueno se hablaba de que él
was making a docuseries
estaba haciendo una una docu serie
too I have no idea if this has
también yo no tengo idea de si esto ha
prospered More than anything because Jesús
prosperado Más que nada porque Jesús
wants a lot of money to do
quiere mucho dinero por hacer cualquier
anything so of course I'm talking to you about one on
cosa entonces claro os hablo de una en
Netflix there was no talk of one What happens is
Netflix no se habló de una Lo que pasa
how they also talk about the fact that they are
como se habla también de que están
making one of Pedro Carrasco okay they
haciendo una de Pedro Carrasco vale se
are talking about docuseries because
están hablando de docu series porque
some work and others don't but Jesús would
algunas funcionan y otras no pero Jesús
not fall for that but the thing is that
no te entraría el trapo de eso pero es
you cannot fall for it because he
que tampoco te puede entrar porque él
as a father with Andrea was not up to the
como padre con Andrea no estuvo a la
task because he did not have to ask
altura porque él no tenía que que pedir
Belén's permission he would notify that he was going to
permiso a a Belén él avisaba que iba se
take his daughter and such he would take her downstairs
llevaba su niña y tal él la bajaba abajo
and then for whatever reason the daughter
y luego por lo que sea la niña allí no
was not comfortable there because I know that once
estaba cómoda porque yo sé que una vez
the daughter called for them to pick her up and
la niña llamó que la fueran a buscar y
her aunt Carmen went to get her okay why
fue su tía Carmen a buscarla vale porque
not then I mean Jesús in that sense he has
no entonces o sea Jesús en ese sentido
not done well another issue is everything
no lo ha hecho bien otro tema es todo lo
that they have put up with from Belén that is
que han aguantado ellos de Belén eso es
another issue but that  he has not behaved
otro tema pero que él no se ha portado
well with his daughter and she has gotten lost A
bien con su hija y se ha perdido Una
wonderful girl Because look, she had her
niña maravillosa Porque fíjate que tenía
life sorted out sitting down At 18 to
la vida resuelta sentándose A los 18 a
talk and she says no mom it's not my
hablar y ella dice no mamá yo no tengo
fault for the life that you have led
la culpa de la vida que tú has llevado
I want to be anonymous she left she did all
yo quiero ser anónima se fue hizo todo
the paperwork to be anonymous to be
el papeleo para ser anónimo para ser
anonymous and that's it but of course it's Jesus she can't
anónima y ya está pero claro es Jesús no
say anything I also tell you one
puede decir nada también te digo una
thing I have an idea in my head that
cosa Yo tengo una idea en la cabeza que
if instead of a girl it's a boy he won't let him
si en vez de una niña es un niño no deja
know what he owes Lenin Look what I'm telling
que se lo que debe Lenin Fíjate lo que
you let's see he doesn't let him keep it
te digo a ver no deja que se lo quede
either that is in his power maybe
tampoco eso está en su poder a lo mejor
not
no
well she would have fought she would have fought
bueno hubiera peleado hubiera peleado
let's say she wouldn't have fought But this
digamos no hubiera peleado Pero esta
neglect that he has had with the girl Well you
desidia que ha tenido con la niña Pues
see the girl is a victim she doesn't
ves la niña es una víctima no se lo
deserve it what happens it's true that the girl
merece lo que pasa es verdad que la niña
is a girl who has a point of
es una niña que tiene un punto de de
coldness of understanding her mother of seeing
frialdad de entender a su madre de ver
everything that her mother has done they say
todo lo que su madre lo ha hecho dicen
that at Belén's wedding with Miguel she made
que en la boda de Belén con Miguel hizo
a beautiful speech giving him his place the
un discurso precioso dándole su sitio la
people well they got very emotional and she is a
gente pues se emocionó mucho y es una
girl Well to  the one that her mother pays a lot of
niña Pues a la que su madre hace mucho
attention and well at the end of the day the one who has
caso y bueno al fin y al cabo quien ha
always been there for her has been her
estado para ella ahí siempre ha sido su
mother with her father he couldn't aim And
madre con su padre no podía apuntar Y
this is how it is that one day
esto es así es que a mí un día
Campanario came to me I told her
campanario me llegó a decir yo le dije
but María José Why isn't Jesus going to see
pero María José Porque Jesús no va a ver
the girl and she told me Joana it's that I don't
a la niña y ella me dijo Joana es que no
know if it's that I tell him go see
lo sé si es que yo se lo digo ve a ver a
Andrea and he doesn't want That's what
Andrea y no quiere Eso me lo dijo a mí
María José told me So this isn't now just
María José O sea que esto no es ahora
talking for the sake of talking, making it up and no at
hablar por hablar inventarse y no en
all it's that she didn't understand it either
absoluto es que ella también tampoco lo
and I told him and he didn't know how to
entendía y se lo decía y él no te sabía
give you any explanation
dar ninguna explicación
she couldn't give you any explanation she
ella no te podía dar ninguna explicación
was the first one who asked for it too so
era la primera que lo pedía también
in that sense she hasn't behaved
entonces en ese sentido no se ha portado
well either then you look at the other thing
bien también lo luego tú miras lo otro
everything that they've had to put up with on
todo lo que han tenido que aguantar en
Sálvame in everything and he got into it with
sálvame en todo y se metía con todo el
everyone with María José with Carmen with her
mundo con María José con Carmen con su
sister-in-law at the beginning it was let's go to Carmen
cuñada al principio fue vamos a Carmen
Janeiro I think Carmen Janeiro ended up doing
Janeiro yo creo que Carmen Janeiro acabó
three waves in a bikini and then
se hizo tres olas en bikini y ya
disappeared because she was fed up that's
desapareció porque acabó harta eso es
something else but there I tell you
otra cosa pero ahí ya te digo a mí me lo
María
dijo María
José told me I tell her  that Andrea goes
José yo le digo que vaya a ver Andrea y
and he tells me that he's not going and I asked him
y él me dice que no va y yo le decía por
why He told me it's that he doesn't give you an
qué Él me decía es que no te da
explanation Of course because as a mother you don't
explicación Claro porque como mamá no te
like it either that he doesn't go see
gusta a ti tampoco que no vaya a ver a
his oldest daughter or his oldest son to
su hija mayor o a su hijo mayor a día de
this day they still maintain a relationship with the
hoy siguen manteniendo relación con la
family
familia
no No man if there is news and I will
no No hombre si hay una noticia y yo les
contact them but María José also
contactaré pero María José también
decided to move away okay And then when
decidió alejarse vale Y luego cuando
she was so sick with the issue
ella estaba tan malita con el tema
of being admitted to the hospital, the
del que la ingresaron el tema de la
fibromyalgia issue, I sent her a message and
fibromialgia yo le puso un mensaje y
she came up with something that I was shocked
ella me salió con una cosa que yo me
and I said really this girl
quedé muerta y dije realmente esta chica
is very bad and thank God I didn't
está muy mal y gracias a Dios a mí no me
have to
tocó
work on issues that she
volver a trabajar temas en los que ella
was involved in if it were my turn then I would call her
estuviera si me tocara pues la llamaría
like everyone else I would try to
como a todo el mundo intentaría
contact her But well, she I suppose that when
contactar Pero bueno ella Supongo que al
the fibromyalgia happened to her over the years
pasarle lo de la fenomenalgia los años
also make you realize that it's not
también te hacen darte cuenta que no
worth getting into fights there
vale la pena entrar en peleas ahí hizo
Andrea did a lot because Andrea was the one who
mucho Andrea porque Andrea fue quien le
asked her mother mom don't talk about
pidió a su madre mamá no hables más de
my father anymore okay And then that has already been
mi padre vale Y entonces pues eso ya se
fixed Of course it has already been fixed
ha arreglado Claro ya se ha solucionado
yes yes
sí sí
let's watch the next video
vamos a ver el siguiente vídeo
look  here also on call
mira aquí también en llamada
on call or yes
en llamada o sí
when she she has not wanted
cuando ella ella no ha querido
Lidia I totally agree with what you
Lidia Estoy totalmente de acuerdo con lo
say she supports me and that's why they
que dices ella me apoya y por eso la
call her from your side but you get
llaman de a tu lado pero llegas el
your phone totally off the subject because
teléfono tuyo totalmente del tema porque
she is Crescentini's friend that nobody
ella la amiga de crescentini que nadie
spoke to Crescentini this is that this
hablaba con crescentini esto es que este
five minute video I can't put it
vídeo de cinco minutos No lo puedo poner
all because of the copyright issue
entero por el tema de los derechos de
But this this because you are like
autor Pero esto esto porque tú eres como
the scourge of Lydia Lozano if I remember correctly no
el azote de lydia Lozano si mal no
no let's see here something happened the truth of
no a ver aquí pasó una cosa la verdad de
This was that when the whole Ylenia issue broke out
Esto fue que cuando saltó todo el tema
to me the director that I had
de ylenia a mí el director que tenía
because people were already hitting her without
porque la gente ya le estaba pegando sin
and I hadn't started the subject told me Hey
y no había empezado el tema me dijo Oye
Joana call her Talk to her I called her She
Joana llámala Habla con ella yo la llamé
thanked me and she told me I'm going to
Ya me agradeció y ella me dijo voy a
ask that they bring you to your side I
pedir que te traigan a tu lado yo la
honestly thought no and well And yes I went to
verdad pensaba que no y bueno Y sí fui a
your side and I was with her and I
tu lado y yo estuve con ella y yo
contacted an investigator that I
contacté con un investigador que yo
knew was serious who had done an
sabía que era serio que había hecho una
investigation on Lenias and
investigación sobre lenias y a
Frankensentini and such And well I was
frankensentini y tal Y bueno yo estuve
there at your side  Since other
allí en a tu lado Como estuvieron otras
people were there, I told you that
personas te dije que estuvo la abuela de
Ylenia's grandmother was there. Albano's brother also came.
ylenia El hermano albano también vino
Well,
Bueno
in the end, one day she called me and said,
ella al final un día me llama y me dice
look Johana, they gave me
mira Johana que me han dado el teléfono
Ylenia's father-in-law's phone number. Okay, he
del suegro de ylenia vale
lives in Santo Domingo. I'm very nervous,
vive en Santo Domingo estoy muy nerviosa
call you. I
llama tú
called. It
yo llamé
was a doctor who told me, "No, I'm not a
era un doctor me dijo No no soy
psychiatrist, I'm a traumatologist." I
psiquiatra soy traumatólogo y yo le
explained to her, "Look, I'm Joana Morillas. We're in
expliqué mire soy Joana morillas en
Spain. We're dealing with this issue of
España estamos con este tema de la hija
Albano and Romino's daughter who has disappeared." She
de albano y romino que ha desaparecido y
said, "Look, we don't know them here, I don't
me dijo mire aquí no los conocemos yo no
know who you are." I mean, they say that one of
sé quién son digo es que dicen que un
your sons is married to her and that
hijo suyo está casado con ella y que
you're treating her. She said, "Well, let's go,
usted la trata y dice pues vamos en
absolutely not." I felt relieved. I said, "
absoluto es y yo ya me alivia y le dije
Lydia, that's not true. If you want, call yourself. I
Lidia No es cierto si quieres llama tú
don't think I called the wrong
no creo que me haya equivocado de
phone number." And that's how it was. Then she
teléfono Y así fue todo y luego ya ella
went to Santo Domingo, she didn't find
fue a Santo Domingo ya no lo no encontró
anything. Well, she came back. They started to
nada ya bueno volvió la empezaron a
hassle her. She was there for a while, and it didn't
machacar Estuvo una temporada aparte no
appear on TV. What happened is that the
salió en la tele y lo que pasa es que la
Santo Domingo lead that was talked about started. It all
pista de Santo Domingo que se habló Todo
started because they
se empezó porque al Mario Romina
hired a private investigator for Mario Romina and
contrataron a un investigador privado y
that investigator started charging.  with
ese investigador salió tarifando con
Albano and Romina he held a
albano y con Romina hizo una rueda de
press conference and said I'm going to Santo Domingo
prensa y dijo yo me voy a Santo Domingo
to look for Romina,
a buscar a Romina a
Ylenia, Ailenia Carresi. Okay, and there was a
ylenia ailenia carresi Vale y había una
soap opera written on the internet that said
novela escrita en internet que salía
this about Santo Domingo getting married, well,
esto de Santo Domingo que se casó que
someone, obviously
esto pues alguien evidentemente que
Telecinco knows who it is because they
telecinco sabe quién es porque le
recorded him on camera and everything, an interview with this
grabaron en cámara y todo una entrevista
person, this man who was also
este persona este señor que además se
called Charlie, I told him his name is
llamaba Charlie yo le dije se llama
Charlie and such, and I spoke with him once
Charlie y tal y yo hablé una vez con él
and because he already let me speak to him
y porque él ya me dejó hablar con él
because he's cold, I told him, hey,
porque tiene frío Yo le dije Oye de
really, get the idea out of this mess because
verdad sacar la idea de este lío porque
this is a mess, don't
es que esto es un embolado que no se
worry, we're going to defend her and such. And
preocupe que la vamos a defender y tal Y
in the end, well, nothing, the one who ate
al final pues pues nada la que se comió
the stories or her and the day that I
las historias o ella y el día que yo
entered there on Sálvame, I told her you're
entré ahí en sálvame que yo le digo eres
a scoundrel, it's because I got
una Sinvergüenza es porque a mí me dio
angry because I was to say, hey, let's
coraje porque yo era para decir Oye a
see,
ver
this is Lidia, she gave you the information, but
está Lidia te dio la información pero
behind Lidia there's a director, there's a
detrás de Lidia hay un director hay una
production. When I go to work
producción yo cuando voy a trabajar a un
somewhere, if it's information that's
sitio si es una información que es
strong, I'm in the habit of talking to
fuerte Yo tengo costumbre de hablar con
my director my director and tell her look I have
mi director mi directora y decirle mira
this my source is this So in
tengo esta mi fuente es esta Entonces en
that sense it wasn't done well instead
ese sentido no se hizo bien ella en vez
of listening she started to get into a
de escuchar empezó a meterse conmigo
fight with me and that's when I jumped in
a pelearse conmigo y yo fue cuando salte
and said you're a scoundrel because it
y le dije Eres una Sinvergüenza porque
seemed cowardly to me to do that
me pareció de cobardes hacer eso
you understand it wasn't right but well
entiendes no estuvo bien pero bueno a
sometimes you know well these
veces uno sabes
are things that
pues son cosas que ocurren
usually happen currently what is your
usualmente actualmente cuál es tu
relationship with Lidia No I don't have she
relación con Lidia No yo no tengo ella a
that day she started sending me messages
mí ese día me empezó a poner mensajes
then they invited me to go to the program but
luego me invitaron a ir al programa pero
we were in a pandemic I said no and she
estábamos en pandemia yo dije que no y
told me queco Hernández I always
que me dijo queco Hernández siempre me
got along very well with him he said but
llevaba muy bien con él me dijo pero yo
Anita you have to come when the
Anita tienes que venir ya cuando pase la
pandemic is over I said Well we'll see and they
pandemia yo dije Bueno ya veremos y me
called me to go for something and I sent
llamaron para ir para algo y yo le puse
a WhatsApp to the idea and I told her that
un WhatsApp a la idea y le dije que
you know that they have called me to go but
sepas que me han llamado para ir pero
that I have said no because the
que yo he dicho que no porque yo la
truth is I also didn't want to continue with a subject that I
verdad tampoco quería seguir con un tema
want to say no no the girl has already been
del que quiero decir no no la niña ya la
officially declared dead and I
declararon oficialmente muerta y ya yo
never said that she was alive and I said that
jamás dije que estaba vida y yo dije que
for me she was missing that's it
para mí Estaba desaparecida ya ya está
that case you start to shoot and they are
que de ese caso empiezas a tirar y son
cases that  they revive every now and then like the case
casos que reviven cada dos por tres como
of Luis Miguel's mother
el de la mamá de Luis Miguel
famous cases of people who have
casos famosos de gente que ha
disappeared and that's it And
desaparecido y
no and there's no more and besides he's not
ya está Y no y no hay más y además no es
very nice because I remember that
muy amable porque yo recuerdo que una
once I called him about something and he knew
vez le llamé por un tema y él sabía
who I was and he said Oh well yes you
quién era yo y me dijo Ah pues sí que
were at your side you were with Lidia
estabas en a tu lado estabas con Lidia
I yes Yes well well very good very good and he
Yo sí Sí bueno bueno muy bien muy bien y
answered what I asked him
me respondió a lo que yo le pregunté
Then I don't know well Lidia Well
Entonces no sé pues Lidia Bueno también
she would also have to say the same thing that I
tendría que decir ella lo mismo que
wanted to say I have a
quería decir yo
hard time with that subject I mean she gets
lo pasa mal con ese tema o sea se pone
clear because she gets scared But it's
Claro porque ya se acobarda Pero es
also true that when a journalist
verdad que también cuando un periodista
has a problem
tiene un problema también es responsable
their director and their section chief are also responsible and everything
su director y su jefe de sección y todo
if the homework wasn't done well it wasn't
si no se hicieron bien los deberes no se
done well you know no then there were
hicieron bien entiendes no luego hubo
journalists that I heard who said
periodistas que yo escuché que decían
Well I sit down and I say what I want I stayed I
Pues yo me siento y digo lo que me da la
said I of course not For
gana me quedé dije yo desde luego no Yo
me let's go never I always say it just like
por mí vamos nunca siempre lo digo igual
if I'm going to comment on a story I
que si yo voy a comentar una información
tell you you understand that I'm here
te lo digo a ti entiendes que estoy aquí
with you because I don't want to get
contigo porque yo no quiero meter en
anyone in trouble You know then Well they
problemas a nadie Sabes entonces Bueno
gave him a lot his colleagues gave him a
le dieron mucho los compañeros le dieron
lot it
mucho
's a  big mistake Yes but but in the end it
es un error fuerte Sí pero pero al final
was Look let's return to the subject of Rocío and
fue fue Mira volvemos al tema de Rocío y
the crazy series in the end it was a lot of money
la loco serie al final fue mucho dinero
and a lot of ratings because if they knew
y mucho rating porque si ellos sabían
that it didn't exist Why did other networks
que no existía Por qué en otras cadenas
make specials? It wasn't garbage, their
hacían especiales no era una basura su
information, I don't
información yo lo que es una basura no
touch it on my channel, I know, I think that something
lo toco en mi canal yo sé creo que algo
is garbage, I don't touch it, what I don't do
es una basura no lo toco lo que no hago
is make 300,000 videos on a topic that
es hacer 300.000 vídeos de un tema que
I know is a lie, that it's garbage and that it
yo sé que es mentira que es una basura y
can hurt people's feelings,
que puede herir la sensibilidad de la
people are very happy with you,
gente en la gente muy contenta contigo
yes, I
sí
have to say that today I'm going to
que tengo que decir que hoy voy a
finish
terminar
the little guy and I'm also going to dispatch it
el canijo y también lo voy a despachar
quickly because I
rapidito porque
have to, I mean, it's going to explode on me. Let's
tengo que o sea me va a petar Algo vamos
watch the third video before I go
a ver el tercer vídeo antes de irme
see.
a ver
Well, all this came about as a result of some
bueno todo esto vino a raíz de una
information that I had in relation to
información que yo tenía en relación a
Pepe and Ivonne in which they came to
Pepe y a Ivonne en la que venían a
tell me that things were not as
decirme que las cosas no eran como las
Ivonne had told them. So I got
había contado Ivonne Entonces yo me puse
in touch with her and I said, Well,
en contacto con ella y le dije Bueno
look, there's this information, I would like to
mira ahí esta información me gustaría
know your opinion, she does not deny it
conocer tu parecer ella no la desmiente
at any time.  but she
en ningún momento la información pero me
tells me no, that she doesn't want to talk about the
dice que no que no quiere hablar del
subject, so well what happens is that
tema entonces Bueno lo que ocurre es que
a few hours go by since I call her
pasan unas horas desde que yo la llamo
on the phone and from that moment on I
por teléfono y a partir de ese momento
start receiving calls with a
empiezo a recibir llamadas con número
hidden number where an unknown voice
oculto donde una voz desconocida que
says, look, it's better if you don't publish this, it's better if this doesn't come to light, and well, everything happens. In this way, did you have any problems because of these statements? Well, it was a really quite unpleasant issue because it was when Ivonne and Pepe were in one of the trials, you
era cuando estaban en uno de los juicios
know that Pepe has always
Ivonne y Pepe sabes que Pepe siempre ha
said that the child was not his son, he did not
dicho que el niño no era hijo suyo no se
want to do the paternity tests,
quiso hacer las pruebas de paternidad lo
Ivonne has tried. Well, this was
ha intentado Ivonne Pues bueno esto era
an issue of paternity tests, of some
un tema de pruebas de paternidad de unas
things that were going on that I'm not going
cosas que había por el medio que no voy
to comment on because I think they would be
a comentar porque creo que serían
problems for the channel, you know, and
problemas para el canal entiendes y a
they would settle it in court,
que se arreglen ellos en los juzgados
but it's true that I received these
pero sí es verdad que yo recibí estas
calls and they weren't pleasant, the
llamadas y no eran no eran agradables la
truth is, they invited me to go to sálvame, I
verdad me invitaron a ir a sálvame lo
thought about it a lot but I said, look, in the end, it's
pensé mucho pero dije mira al final lo
best to tell it because also if
mejor es contarlo porque también si
someone intends to scare you by
alguien tiene intención de asustarte
telling them, they'll  you take this off and
diciéndole ya le quitas de esto y
effectively once I got out there
efectivamente una vez salí allí ya no
the lawsuits didn't come up again you know
volvieron a salir las demandas sabes
but it's been one of the most
Pero ha sido uno de los temas más
unpleasant, heaviest topics more what years have I
desagradables más heavys más qué años he
done
hecho
this what year is it well this I don't know this
esto qué año es pues esto yo que sé esto
was Ivonne on a in a reality show
estaba Ivonne en un en un reality
I remember a reality show that was a Big
recuerdo un reality eso fue un gran
Brother no that was a Survivor
hermano no eso hace ya un supervivientes
Ivonne was there too no I don't know I don't
estuvo Ivonne también no no lo sé No lo
know yes but but I
sé sí pero pero
was on a Big Brother in a Big
estuve en un gran hermano en un gran
Brother
hermano
that Antonio Caparrós was also on I
que estuvo también Antonio caparrós eso
remember dad Rosa was there Alonso
lo recuerdo papá Rosa estuvo Alonso
Alonso Caparrós was yes And the truth is it's
Alonso caparrós estuvo sí Y la verdad es
a very very unpleasant topic and I think
un tema muy muy desagradable y yo creo
that people have stopped talking about it and
que ya la gente ha dejado de tratarlo y
also since he is legally Ivonne and Pepe's son he has
además como el hijo de Ivonne y de Pepe
put so much thought into the
legalmente lo es ha puesto tanta cabeza
issue in fact Look I don't even want a
al tema de hecho Mira yo no quiero ni
pension and or my last name is Reyes and I don't
pensión y o de apellidos soy Reyes y ni
want to inherit nor do I want to know anything about
quiero heredar ni quiero saber nada de
this man and he's a child who works and
este señor y es un niño que trabaja y se
makes a living and very well the truth Very
busca la vida y muy bien la verdad Muy
well very well very well
bien muy bien muy bien
[Music]
[Música]